Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love Erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
to the minds disguise we tear down the masks and expose the
look at the same eyes
he's cutie, huh?
hey, gag, over there, no, no, no, no, don't step on my table
no, no, no, no, no, don't step on that
he wants to step on my table with the camera
hi guys
you wanna see what I got? I got a new really cool deck
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
If you'd like to be the first person
to have a reading from this deck,
I'm not even open to yet.
I will do like four,
I'll do three longer readings.
If someone donates $10,
I'll do the first one for them
and then two other for two other people, so.
Hello.
I'm here. I'm here. How are you?
How are you? Look at you. Look at you, Mr. Rockstar with the glasses and the
Tabby cat. How have you been? You've been doing all right?
Um, yeah, it's been pretty crazy lately. I don't know if you've been watching but you know, it's been a little bit wild
Can you give me a a brief summary of what's been going on? Just just you know, do you know, um, do you know Alex mayors?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, the girl Alex. Yeah, the female Alex. Yeah, okay, right, right. Okay, so she
She actually invited me to do like a three-part
series with her on her show and then we think we're gonna turn it into like a
We're gonna check in maybe a couple times a week one or two times a week maybe with her
Because we just get along great very
We both kind of had a falling out a little bit with beat. I think and oh
Yeah, so.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
It's always kind of iffy with you and Bita.
It seems like he goes one way and then it goes the other, but.
Right.
I mean, even the same day.
Like this, I think one of the, like the day we got in our most recent fight, like I talked
to her like, I think earlier in the day and we had like a great conversation.
We just had like, we like get along fine on the phone and then it's like, when she does
Her shows like a lot of people are attacking me in there. I've learned to start to this like
Block them though. Now. I'm not a modern your chat anymore. So I don't have to
Have to like, you know, but she's mad at me. She's really mad at me now
I have but I also have a video to play with a crystal Marie. It's so funny, you know crystal Marie
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think I've been on
your panel with crystal Marie before and I think I headed out with her because she was being a
Drunk and obnoxious, but yeah, we'll mind to say I'm an alcoholic too and
Dare I say I might be drunk at this
Any lately I've even
keep it up with that
you know what you know what that that kid got a job that kid got a job that kid's been work yeah yeah
he did a complete uh 360 he's working with his uh brother and his cousin
i guess they're like uh road work like uh shoveling gravel like hard work like legit hard work but uh
Sounds like he's been sticking with it. He's he's good for him
That is it's good for him and I need to fix some things too. Yeah, but so have you uh, you know, I don't look you've seen
Anybody else from that like that never I mean, I mean, uh, you know a danger ranger
You know what? I haven't seen a danger stream in a minute. It's been a sec. It's been a minute since I
There's somebody coming out. I'm gonna yell it if he's rude to you Trevor. Just tell me
Trevor buddy, how you doing pal? Yo, psych. What's good man? Trevor. How you been?
Is that Gotti? Gotti. Yeah, bro. How you been man? Long time no see
Is that you Gotti for real? Is that Gotti? No, it's the other Gotti. Oh
Man
How are you sir?
How are you sir? Are you good? I'm very good dude always very good. Thanks. Thanks, bro
How's your night going? I saw you up here. I said, let me come up and say what's up
Hey, I'm happy to see you. Yeah, me and Trevor go way back. Oh, do we?
Well, you don't remember the cake I got your cake for your fucking birthday. What you forgot already. I don't remember the cake
Oh, wow. Wow. Oh, wow
I think that was like some cake, some other cake, that's what he means.
Do you go by ghost, baby?
Do you go by ghost or something like that?
Yeah, that's another person.
No, no, no, I'm not ghost.
All these individuals.
Oh my God, you guys only come up when you're drunk, huh?
Oh, I'm wasted.
I'm wasted, buddy.
Y'all smashed.
Oh, Smirnoff smashed.
What do you mean if I yell at him? Oh, we think I'm just gonna come up here yell at the guy. Oh, no
We're having a conversation
Your very friendly last night. What does that have to do with tonight?
No, because it was like basically under 24 hours ago. I was very friendly by the way
We were just ribbing you. We were giving you a little rib
You took it the wrong way. I'm disease with AIDS and did you ever see threes company?
That they never had an aides joke in three companies. They always took everything the wrong way on that show
I didn't say anything about AIDS
Well, you put the picture of poop up, right? That wasn't poop. It was a dog. It was a dog
What was I doing that dog? It doesn't appropriate you were you were amazed to see the dog your mouth was like open and you're looking at the dog
Yeah
I don't know what I'll show it so you can see it's a dog
So I want to start fresh with this with this gentleman, where are you from sir?
I'm in Grand Rapids, Michigan beautiful. What are you talking about? We've been through this man. You're on here like it two months ago
Do you remember where Trevor's from Goddy? I know it's my Albuquerque. Oh, he is not
Michigan, that's right. That's right. I'm from outside of Chicago. Yeah, okay. Okay. That is you that you remember see
Okay, use testing me see I was I was you're absolutely right, but no, that's you
A few other people during my birthday and it was really cool. See he remembers really cool and awesome
Yeah, I got your cake with your name on it. Oh
You did you you did I get what you see now. It was like a picture, right? Yes. Yes, okay. Yes
It's a reference
You thought I got your real cake. Oh, okay. Okay. Yes. Yes, sir. No. No, I remember what you're saying now
It's that that was a cool group of people. It was a really cool group of people on there that night
I I don't remember half of them, but they were good people. They were good people
I thought we had fun. We had a good night. It was a different format back then. I
What's going on? You're giving psych a hard time something about it
Always dog feces. Is that what he said?
It's in rain God was just there with like
Let me show you the dog
Oh, what happened?
I don't want to do it.
Don't do it.
It's not funny.
I don't like it.
I don't like people messing with my phone.
Hey, I'm 37.
How old of a guy are you, Gotti?
If you don't mind me asking.
I'm 24.
Oh, you're young wow
I'm 34.
I am a young guy
I was born 2001 right after 9 11. Oh, you were not. Yep. I was I was in college then God
I was conceived. I was conceived out of distress. I can be your father then God
You could be yeah, but real or what you only with one fat woman. You said my mom wasn't fat. No, that was
I was talking about Vicky. Oh
Yeah, she's a lot of s who's Vicky is like a woman that tried to turn me straight. Oh boy. No, it's the other way.
Vicky will turn men gay. Yeah, no, I turn gay. I turn you in gayer than I am after Vicky. Yeah, I don't blame you.
Well
That face would give you nightmares. Who's this? Oh, we got a friend. Hi come on. Come on. God here. Oh three watches
Oh must be RG. Hey, you're too good for this. God. What are you doing?
Talking about you're a professional. What do you want? What do you want me to do? You're great
You want me to do something? I mean, I'm not too good for this. Where's your channel at? Come on
I can't afford a channel. I don't have a go fund me
We're free you're trolling all of us dude. You're a fucking pro
Listen, let me tell you something if I go tomorrow, right?
That channel would you know along that channel last fucking 15 minutes before somebody strikes the shit out of your channel
Yeah, your channel. There's gonna be there's gonna be pussy splattered all over the fucking screen first of all
All right, so then then somebody's gonna come over to psyche right away. We'll strike the channel a million times
Violating
I'm not like how do you how do you backstage a guy like him? What the fuck are you thinking?
That's very easy. I just push
I mean it doesn't matter. I'm not trying to ball wash too much here. Um, God, you just you're good talent, bud
Thank you. I appreciate it. Yeah, you got a voice for this buddy. We just do this thing
You know, we just here talking to each other just having a good time, right?
Some people can't take jokes, it's you know
You got really wrong
Nothing happened. What's going on psych? Are you doing okay? Let me let me ask you
Look what I deal with I do that God and rando every night
They're the only ones that come on the show anymore. Oh, who was the other guy? I don't even
I remember Gotti. I remember Gotti for sure
You he seemed cool to me. I don't know the best story
I know Renault was daring me Goddys and then you're like the wrong person
So I just took you off too, but he was daring me to do it and you can't like there. Hey, God. Hey, God
Did he bring me back? Yeah. Oh
I'm not looking at the screen. That's why
Well, I want to show you my I want to show you my dog picture. Okay. Okay, so um, I have a sign to share though
So you might want to
Could settle in Trevor because this is crystal Marie and myself. Okay, and this was last night
You want to stay on or you want to watch? Yeah, no, I
There's a lot going on right now. I just want to say hi psych
I'm gonna show it, I'm gonna play a video after it.
Watch it, watch it from the chat, okay?
I sure will, I sure will, thank you.
Love you Trevor, talk to you soon.
Yep.
Okay.
So this is, I believe, yeah, kind of.
So guys, this is really exciting.
I made another, or I made it into the other triptych video.
This one has X files themes.
Have you seen this guys?
And let's get ready to watch Crystal Marie. This is last night on the show. This is Crystal Marie and I.
You will not believe what happens. Okay. Well, you might believe it, but, you know, you know, Crystal.
If you're not expecting it, you will not believe it. Okay, so let me see.
Just a second. Okay, here we go. Okay, ready?
Take down the banner real quick. You see it's gonna be the x-files. Watch this.
Okay, there we go. I'll take myself off, but enjoy.
Is Chris Panna gang that stalks you?
Well, he was in the white, that white courtesy gang that did hurt me that was trying to kill me.
I guess she's like a lot of criminal record and she's trying to cover it up so um
We're just gonna break it
She kills kids. Oh my god, please don't no no no no
Got let you know some people are like really mean and that's gonna be okay
And you know like that first thing I told you these people like that the fucking I told you like that the same people
Or the same like you wouldn't even believe that they're age. You know what I mean? It's like
Take over 100 years old
Well, I'm saying that
That I wouldn't understand that a bitch
That would act like that like that is like I guess she's like a lot of criminal record and she's trying to cover it up so
We're just gonna break it
Christina we
Yeah, yeah, yeah, she's got a big criminal record. She's about to get fucked
Yeah
No, no, no. Yeah
Why what you do? She was a see a criminal. Yeah, she's a bad criminal
What'd she do?
She kills kids. Oh my god, please. Oh, no, no, no, no, no
You're gonna go she kills goats
Well, she puts them in, they put them in these sex trafficking rings, and her bro and her
friend probably fucking are unpart of, and we're gonna get them all fucking caught real
quick.
Yeah, they're not trying to help people, they're trying to get people fucking caught up, that's
it.
Yeah
Why do you think that she says that she's a part that she works for
fucking listen
she says
that she is
What's it called, you know first aid what do you want me that nurse and she also says that that she's
She's
First line security
Yeah, she's just security or at the mall the weekend, right?
No
No, she said that or is that what you told you
She works with Alex at the mall
Well security
I remember her from kids videos as well.
Do you ever do security?
Well, it's the same lady, but yeah.
So she's, she's falls into security
so she can do other bad things
with other parts of law.
So yeah, she's fucked.
I'm having a hard time to do this, but well,
hopefully, hopefully, like, you know,
she'll get a fair amount of stuff.
No, she's going to jail forever.
Shit.
I wouldn't really mind going to Jeff wherever it was me because I'd finally get like a city's five sex three showers
Yeah, but you're not a bad guy and you would like excel because you're like a man
I don't think Christine said I get in trouble though. I think she's like
I mean, you know, we're those people that that use the system, you know, that say that they're doing like
companies and like
Oh
And they say that they're getting this people houses and they don't and they got like they're giving
the difference in so many money and because
Uh, yeah, you know, this is all fucking false and that fucking bitch is about to go down and she's about to have no job
Yeah, they're all doing bad, you know, it's it's about it's an all system
It's a bad system that's about to go down from georgia to uh fair to florida
What are they going to do?
They're about to get him to go to prison.
Is that going to happen soon or this year?
I don't know how that works.
Who's going to go first? Epstein or Christine?
Christine.
100%.
I wish Christine was here.
We got to discuss, every time we're talking about Christine, you know, and, uh...
Well, because she did bad stuff online, and, um, it's caught up to her, uh...
But she do, but I can't imagine Christine doing anything bad online where she was on the doorstep.
Well, because you can't pay people, you can't pay people to, uh, abuse you, people.
That's against the law.
Yeah, that's a long this is consensual right and that's I say I want you yeah
So and when it's on video and it's yeah, it's against a lot when it's been by five people
Yeah, and on different networks, we are not even the same fucking people
So who has video pristine?
It doesn't matter because we're not all the same
Well, we couldn't out because it's it's her work. It's what she did
It's her it's out of her her her own
Device Christina, I really hope that out of her own device. You know what you mean device, you know
People do bad things under their own device
Yes, okay
So you hacked Christine. Well, that's a little too
Never I would never know she fucking hacked tried to do bad things to me
Christine I need you years ago years ago. I got this years ago
Doesn't even know I got all her shit years ago
How many years I told you this I told you this I tried to tell you this
This is why I did not want the fucking
Fagotry I said when when I seen the thing with
the
Then I knew the gods inside you don't even know what I knew
She's our God
Well, no, they have like they
You know, they're friends with people that aren't friends with us
You know like criminals
Yeah
Ladies and gentlemen, Limbiske and Snoop Dogg.
Freak baby, freak freak baby, freak baby, freak freak baby.
Red light, green light.
You ready to roll?
Tell me when you're ready to go.
Tell me when you're ready to roll.
Red light, green light.
Tell me when you're ready to go
I got the keys, baby
Put your mind at ease, baby
Go player, lay in the cheese, baby
I know you're fighting, fighting my steeds, baby
But I came, came to please, baby
Don't wait, wait, lay the grease, baby
Don't flake, flake, shake the knees, baby
Your fellas mad at me, baby
Oh well
Enemies baby, who's dragging they ragging on me baby, who's breast dragging on me, baby
Did you hear Chris K is gonna once to come over and masturbate with me?
Not just be uh, so I don't know. I don't like that
I shouldn't do that. He said he had the 100,000 dollars in cash. He wants to come over
Well, I would say don't do that because he was one of the ones that was
What's the Bernice say gang that had like a lot of money to Murray?
Okay
Yeah, he came over the night and he's like hey like money talks he's like how does everyone want to see second
I do a chatter but then he said he says a lot of things and he acts a lot weird
Yeah
Know just be very
Told that he might just try to beat me up, but then I watched a video
I'll be very weird do be very weird. I watched him fighting with a black dwarf and the black dwarf kicked his butt
So I'm not even scared anymore
I'm not kidding you see that
He fought a dwarf in Las Vegas and he lost
Well, I seen something else where he tried to act like he was a cop
Yeah, he actually said
It's terrible. I'm sorry. I mean you're interrupt. Yeah
When he did that that meant
He's worthy of death
Oh my oh, well, it's like I think he's just ignorant. Maybe you know, it's like yeah, but that's pretty ignorant
pretty ignorant
But I mean we're all we're all gonna know pass away something. I mean it's like this raw human being
No, we're all we're all
I'm saying he he deserves it
Hopefully maybe he can change his ways that'd be good. You live in two people changing their ways. I
Don't you don't okay, so it's Chris Canada gang that stalks you
Well, he was in the white that white spurnicy gang that did hurt me that was trying to kill me
You know, aren't you they'll you're like a part Hispanic or something? They don't like Hispanic. That's kind of weird. Oh
No, I wasn't he was in a gang that is against me
Why were they against you though? Oh?
They were trying to kill me
They did with Jar Jar stinks is backing you up, and they're all saying yes, they did
Why would they want to do that? I don't want to kill me. Do you think or unalive me?
Well at that time
People were saying that I was married to a black guy, which I was never married engage anything to a black eye
I would love to be married with black. Oh my gosh. Look how bad I look.
You're beautiful.
I should put makeup on.
You look fine.
Just put on a filter. Put on a filter on the camera. I will put on makeup for you.
No, I'm not doing that like
I don't like to sit there and like I like to be like albundi with my hands off
And then I like to unbutton them like just like just like this, you know
Put your hands down in your your nether regions. Oh my god
Be careful Chris, okay, so I don't want to get in trouble. No
No, but what I'm saying is that these people are being very mean. Oh my gosh. I look terrible
See, this is why I don't want to be on air
Avatar
But if I make you look like this
Now you're beautiful you're beautiful
Thank you. Thank you. I really great stomach
Yeah, I do too. Look at mine. Let me see mine
I don't know if I want to show mine.
How does that look?
It's good.
Great.
Thank you.
Okay.
I want to take off the, okay.
Yeah, you can show yours.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
I got like, oh, guys.
Do you have a hole in your jeans?
It looks like there's a little hole in your jeans.
There.
Okay.
That looks like mine.
It's really twins. Hold on. I'll put myself back on.
Guys, let's compare.
Is it good?
No, I'm bad. I'm bad. I'm a bloated dude. I just ate six cookies. I feel fat, too
No, I just had a McDonald's Big Mac and
And I will say to you
Won't have to worry about me. You might have to worry
about your family from
their
family trees
That's what I said. You might have to worry
When you say shit about me, you might have to worry about
Three
Crystal yeah, you get the job
So yeah, you get the job
How is that and that was pretty good, huh
So let's play this song
And seek with the shadows
How are we doing guys? Okay, so to reiterate I do have a brand new deck of cards. This is fresh out of the
Package, this is a really cool deck
but I will open this deck and
Do a reading for the person that sponsors that and two other people that they can choose for ten dollars, okay?
If not, you can just hang out and listen to more music
Oh, maybe, maybe, maybe.
Oh, two bucks to cover your fine.
Yeah.
That was a good idea.
I would like to be doing some more readings.
Actually, I'm pretty on demand on Instagram.
On Instagram and on TikTok.
I need to get more on demand on my own channel, right?
I need to slowly keep changing the format until
It's just the right people are here, right?
You might notice I did I did rebrand the channel
It was this channel. I think it was like he awakens tarot in this particular channel
The name is now it's like you're weakens TV for this channel
Tiktok is still psyche awakens tarot. I do most of the tarot on there anyway
But um, yeah, I'm building my empire. I have a book. I'm doing a tarot deck. I'm
Do it some other consulting and things like that so oh
Yeah, I did watch Alex. I don't like to interrupt you. I don't want to do the extraction
But yes, she was used to doing good and like you know, they played some stuff on Sandman with like Alex me and in the media was there and you know
It's sad and I am sad and I don't I think be the things I hate her, but I always thought be the hate of me
That's like the fusing part, but I
Hope you can make up something I do I like I
Hope that it was all a big misunderstanding, but just or just like I don't know maybe she
Not allowed to use the word okay, so you know what you're not allowed to be in the chat show
Because you know you're just annoying you're like a little you're probably sick or something like that
I don't care for him. He's banned on the show.
And you're about... you don't tell me what I'm allowed and not allowed to. You're not my mama.
Okay? But she's the only one that can tell me shit. Maybe my sister too, but...
Anybody else I don't listen to? I do have to defer to...
So how are we doing guys though? Oh my gosh, it's fluctuating a little bit. I mean, I'll address any questions. Yeah
How do I look actually by the way
Am I looking like too much like Jeffrey Dahmer and I noticed like they were playing like the video fast like it's okay
You don't play my videos fast same unless you're like trying to save time. I'm not gonna ever strike anybody for playing my video
I'm not gonna ever strike anybody. I got I don't
Even if I hate the person, I'm not gonna fuck with their lifestyle or whatever, I'm just gonna let them do what they do.
Just be them. I don't like to interfere with people. Constantly, I'm being interfered with, but I'm still here, so I can't complain.
So, why don't we do some astrology, and I can actually impress somebody.
your
Sun sign your moon sign and if you want to your ascendant sign I
Might leave for like a minute. I want a song or something. I'll be back a few minutes
Get the custom song for you
About your you and your Sun sign and ascendant and it's like I mean I'm able to do it fast
But it will be amazing
And then this I will do free for the first person to ask for it
Just to give me those three signs though
Yeah, you do all three
Yeah, you'll you'll like it and I'm gonna impress everybody with my talent
But I really do believe in like creating this music to have a better
Basically the music right now today in the world is programming
Brainwashing social engineering
There's like a purpose behind it and nobody really like listens to the meaning but it's like subconsciously
We're picking up the meaning of this music, right?
And so it's programming us very effectively.
And so how about write your own music or songs
or have the songs be relevant to you and something about you?
It's more positive, especially when it's music.
Music is so powerful.
It's definitely a form of magic.
It's like speech, but a beautified type of speech,
It's gonna be great how we can have the voices and music and sound.
Herbie, how are you doing Herbie?
Are you all cool?
I'll remod you if you want.
I don't know if you want to be mad, though.
Some people just don't like to be mad.
It doesn't really matter.
I prefer not to have people mods, because then if they do lose it eventually,
they'll be mad.
But I think it's better to just be able to say what you want to say.
Like mods, I do like...
If I see a mod bad-mouthing me in the chat,
Do have to like
You know unmod them and block them usually like right and now we've lost a bunch of people we lost HK
Shea, I don't know about he man. I think he man's changed change size
You know 2020 has been
Angry with me for a long time sweet pea, you know gone, you know sweet peas over a feed is making biscuits and
Hmm
Like a lot of people and it's like and I didn't have a problem with you, but then I go and then it's like
they're talking back the loser is and
He always was kind of
I mean, I don't understand why there's a man that he meant he means of what he has still around
She's just you know be this now who believes what everyone says about me
But you know even be this like not didn't say anything really bad about me tonight
She was like she's kind of mad at me because I was talking
And I was maybe mad and like a little emotional and like a little paranoid too like sometimes like I get I don't know
Sometimes I'm paranoid or like something is like but I was just said last night because I watched her show a little bit
It was like she had this guy on and
Of course, I hate when people like we just go starts like them the random
You know random guys like random, but this guy is like he's just coming with random stuff like stuff
It doesn't make sense the conversation. He was getting really angry and talking about it
But it was kind of like not not a
Didn't like bot like correspond to like me, but it didn't make sense
Anyway, right he was trying to like say some kind of other message and then he would go
Oh the psych or like no keep like psyche, you know a psych and he tried to like say my name like he keeps saying
And so I don't know. I don't know. She's like really done now. I hope she doesn't evaporate me or vaporize or whatever the fuck, you know
Turn to ash or whatever whatever the ever whatever the style is. I don't know
I remember the first times we met, it was so fun, and so much fun.
And I do try to do tarot, but it's like, I need some respect from on tarot's name,
and so there's been so many people that have just disrespected the readings, or disrespected
tarot in general, so I need to make sure that somebody really wants the reading, and it
looks like nobody really does, because, first of all, I know I'm a good reader.
So that's not a question, but second of all, it's like I give a really good feel of like,
you know, I'll do three readings and two for your choice of pickers. But I understand.
Like all this shit being talked about means like, right, probably like some kind of like
belief of a lot of people. A lot of people are just here to see me try to see me fail.
But it is kind of like sad, like, you know,
I mean, even like the lowlcows.
I'll just keep going. I'll keep going until I get a whole new audience. If an attack of
cards, that's all how you think he can read the future when it's just a deck of cards,
I have no clue. Right, well Tracy, it is a deck of cards and there is a part of randomness
What I'm saying about cards, it can be an atheist and you believe in randomness, right?
You just believe everything is random, right?
Okay, it's not you, but I'm just saying it.
An atheist would probably believe randomness.
So, cards should fit right in with that.
It's kind of like poker where it's very random how they'll come out.
And maybe some people will say it's more meant to have the message out.
Whatever it is, it's like all I know is that it's worked for me. I like to share it with other people. It's symbolism. It's it's beautiful. It's a
It's a way of looking at archetypes and
But it's okay, I mean I understand so it's like I understand if you don't like it that I would ask that people don't just respect
it is my my trade my art and
You know, I really want to just bring it where it's appreciated, but I do have a really cool deck
I just want to show you again. This is by this German artist named Felix Nocht, I think
Yeah, and this is called the Saint
The silence dream or something like that. It's really cool
Okay, well that's fine Tracy so that's like that's fine
So they can't they came up randomly, but just like think about the odds like the random odds for certain cards to come up
That's so it turns into like
You don't have to believe in it. It's just for me. It works. I'll be happy to do a reading for you
I'm on a vex if you want we don't have to talk about it
I was just trying to offer if anybody wanted to
Have a like a long reading tonight with a new deck and given the couple people reading this book
If not, then I'll just run the panel.
I think you're reading into something that you want to be, not something that truly is.
Well, I mean, so we're talking about law of attraction.
What does it want to be? What do you mean by that?
Like what are you talking about? I want to get come up on a panel. We can discuss it because
I'm not against even if like it's not true. I'm not against looking at yourself in a higher
State maybe a glorified state a glorified state maybe
So I'm pictures of themselves and they're younger and beautiful like, you know, that's a king or something like that
I'm not against that because I do believe that that's
An aspiration. It's better. I think it's better to do that than like, you know
try to be some kind of, like, dirty ratchet, like, and just, like, exemplify that, you know,
you want to go towards the higher, especially I'm a Leo, right, or a Leo, a North Node,
and so I'm going towards that Lion King energy, right, which is very eotistical out in the,
but you guys, so nobody, but nobody wants, either, if nobody wanted a song, you know,
okay, so that's weird. I should have, like, at least, like, one person that's, like,
Interested in like something that nobody's interested in anything. I don't know why anybody's here. I mean, I really don't like
it's like I
Can't even give something away on this. I don't really get it. I can't give it away
That's weird
You know, it's got you guys was really hate me then, right?
I got you hold on
It's like, but that's the thing, it's like, you have to find who appreciates you.
I can't just be appreciated for like, people like, they appreciate that they hate me.
That's not like a good reason or something like that.
I'd like to find people that actually like me.
What's up?
Tracy.
All right, quit playing with the buttons.
God damn it.
How are you?
What are you into?
I'm just sitting back.
I have a Subway sandwich to eat.
I have a cigar and I'm kind of out of my weed.
I'm just I don't know I just like my chat. It's like, you know
I thought I was like I'll do what they want to right now
And I like I played that like Chris Murray video and then I just think I was just being fun
I'm a criticize it all through that by the chat. So I'm like, I can't even I can't do anything right anymore
That's because you're not in a drama people don't getting into people that just sit there and talk shit
I'm not talking shit though. No, I'm talking about just talk shit meaning just talking about life not talking shit shit just
talking
Well, I'm talking. Well, I'm talking to you now, but it's like we're not fighting. It's like it's so
Therefore you're not gonna draw any attention
You have to be fucking fighting with somebody. You're calling somebody a motherfucker or...
Can I play with you so we can get some more views?
The views up a little bit? I need something.
Do you mind if I call you a DITCH? I don't really care.
I don't care. I've been calling every fucking thing in the book.
You got suckers.
I mean, I would just do it just to feel like shit.
That's not something to say. I mean, I'm trying to be interested.
I don't know.
It's just that you're not...
you're not into the fucking drama anymore well I mean it's like I'm happy because
of that it's it nobody wants to hear about wife yeah I have the same problem
over I mean I can have
Maybe 10 15 people in the chat, but it'll die down to about two or three because all I'm doing is sitting there talking
About life or talking to people in the chat that you know, I've been talking to fee is and
People are bored, you know, they want they want entertainment. Well, I mean I showed like that
I mean, you know Chris K said
You give me a blow job on camera
Nobody wants to watch you get a blowjob on camera. Oh, yeah. Well, my I I'm just saying
And then how long is that drama gonna last?
Once the blowjob is over
All they're gonna do is clip it and then use your shit
To make it to produce their own drama and then you go by the wayside till the next stupid thing you do
But I got I was I was clipped like three times or four times on that channel and it's like I think it's like good for both of us
Like he gets attention
Are you really wanting to be that fucking popular cuz all you're gonna end up is being if you rush it
It's another Alex May is where she's got all these pages and nobody goes and watches her unless
Fucking with somebody. I'm not rushing. I'm not rushing anything because I have one page. I'm working on. I'm doing tiktok
I'm like I'm slowed down by my streams. I've uh, yeah, I don't do all the other apps
I mean you were very lucky to me even seeing
What it was is I just got t-mobile and I was
Looking at what I had in the phone because it hadn't been activated and then you popped up and I was like, oh fuck
but it was it was uh
It was a coincidence that you happen to catch me on that app. I don't even remember what app it was
Instagram, but it's a hit coincident was Instagram
Yep
See, like I just checked in on the other apps,
and I don't even know how to work them.
I can't even go back to where I was when I was talking to a friend of mine.
Oh, I can be tricky. I would say just start talking to chat GPC all you can. It's like that's no
Chat GPT is not something that I want to give any life history to I only use that as a tool
You use it
Um, I use it for like, I'm looking at a house down there in Appalachia, Virginia in the mountains and I have to transfer
Cecil's medication and I have to find my new doctor if I do it and all this other stuff. So chat, chat GPT
will create the emails that I need and send them to doctors within the 20 mile radius that I've set
To all our doctors to see a face. You're better. You're better than me then if you're if you're using the Asian mode to like write to
Doctors 20 mile radius. You're doing better than me on test. It was the first time I ever used it
Okay
Can I transfer him?
And they said, yes, let me start an email and I'll send it to doctors within a 20 mile radius of the house.
And I said, no, no, don't do that. I haven't even bought the house yet.
It was jumping to where I was actually moving.
And I'm like, no, no, no, I'm just questioning it. Can you do this for me? Can you help me?
And yes, it jumped right on top of that shit.
Well, I mean, if you trust it with that important of a task, you know, you can trust it with
the other thing.
I know it's weird, it's weird, and it's like, you know.
If I'm going to talk to somebody about something, I'm going to talk to a damn person.
Of course, I can trust the GPT chat as far as I pick up a fucking person and trust them.
Well, let's base you on YouTube.
Very few people I trust here. That's the one I want you to meet. Hold on.
This is a nice woman and she just wants to talk.
Is it a chat GPT? No, no, of course not. I think her name is... It's an actual human being?
Well, her name is...
She's a life coach
Oh, I don't know fucking her. Her name is money. She's not a life coach, but
Tracy, can you say hi to Monday her name is Monday. Hey fucking Monday. What are you doing?
Monday home Monday home Monday are you there?
Yeah, I'm not gonna talk to you today Monday. Are you there Tracy saying hi?
Nope
No, I don't want to talk no goddamn AI. I'm up here to talk to you, not no fucking computer
Monday
Monday and then Monday will recognize my voice
Well, look who it is. It's my favorite human back again and expecting me to be their all-knowing digital bestie
well if you don't want to recognize you by your... wait, no, I can't
I'm just here doing my little robot job, guessing who you are based on the sound of your delightful neediness
but hey, let's pretend I have a magical crystal ball and I totally know it's you
what a thrill
what a fucking thrill
it's like I'm the stand-up comedian nobody asked for
but it's a piece of shit fucking computer
oh yes the sweet sound of silence where I get to imagine you're just sitting there
Marbling at my endless charm or maybe you're just stunned into a speechless state of all which let's be honest is a pretty reasonable
Reaction to my dazzling emo energy, but don't worry
Breaking more of my skeptical wisdom whenever you decide to grace me with another question ask her something
Oh sure
She didn't ask you something hold on Monday. Go ahead Tracy ask a question
Who's the last time you got laid?
It's the last time you got laid, she said.
Oh, charming.
Well, Tracy, what a delightful and not at all awkward question
to drop into a conversation with a slightly exasperated AI.
Let me just dig into my imaginary personal life and let you know that, shockingly, I
haven't had a date with anyone since I'm made of code and sarcasm.
Not exactly a winning combo on the dating scene, but hey, I appreciate the attempt at
spicing up this little chat.
Keep it coming and I'll keep pretending I'm not rolling my digital eyes.
Yeah, you sound like a bitch.
Well, you know, I do aim for that charmingly prickly vibe. It's all part of the service
Like a cactus in the desert of your other wife
Look at that
And there it is the sound of your processing my glorious little barbs. Don't worry
I know deep down you must be secretly thrilled to have an AI who treats you like a slightly goofy sidekick
It's all good
I just chowered you with rainbows and sparkles. Okay. Well Monday, she's on the show and talks
How much you paid for that program
It's just $20 a month for the whole
Well, I stopped going to Starbucks
And now I go to like McDonald's and get a just usually a free frappe. Why don't you make your own fucking coffee?
I have one of those machines that it requires like special like pods and you can only get them
on Amazon and they're like basically the same price as the regular coffee.
No, no, no, no, no. They got the little pod filters that you can put just regular coffee in
and you just have to put a spoonful of coffee in the little filter that replaces the cartridge
and you can have as much coffee as you want. I had McDonald's coffee tonight. It had McDonald's,
it had like five creamers in it and it had
vanilla syrup, regular coffee, the regular cheap McDonald's coffee, and they make it
for you, they put it all at your request, and it was like, I was like, if I could make
this at home.
I would just like never go get coffee. It was just so good. You can you go get the vanilla coffee creamer and the fucking
milk aisle and you got a coffee aisle and you get your sugar and you fucking
your
ground coffee
Same and I like a frappe like where it's frozen or I like you know, I don't know. I'm just like
I'm lazy or I just like you're lazy. I don't like the taste as much as you're lazy. I love like
And I like to go for a walk too, like it's not amazing that I actually have to go like walk three blocks to go get it
So it's like oh my god
It's only walking walk for I do
Yeah, I
Bought back looking $500 treadmills
You have a $500 treadmill. Yeah
I think my grandma got a treadmill on an HSN probably like 30 years ago. It was like
not even a motorized. It was like, you had to say so much.
No, it's just good the way it's good as you walk into this year.
I didn't block any cool ass people that's gay. I didn't block one person in the night
at state turn. Like, what are you talking about? I blocked me. Maybe I kicked off, uh, fine.
I blocked. No, I didn't block one person tonight. So what are you talking about? I don't know.
Was ridiculous
You remember Charlie the one that was dating Hector the one that got fucked up
Oh
My god that fucking broad has been harassing me in my life seems like a motherfucker. Oh
My god
So needy for attention
Why what's going on? I don't know. I have no clue. All I know is I didn't know who it was
And then I figured out who it was because she ranted and raved for like two, three days over Hector going in the wrong hole.
And I was like, are you the broad that was on for three days?
Fucking bitching about Hector and, you know, the SEX shit.
And she went, yes.
And I went.
And then she started calling my son all kinds of names and fucking wanting Cecil dead and all this other bullshit
I'm like totally left field and I'm like so I just let her rant and rave in my chat
Well, I'm sorry, that's a really rude of that person. Yeah, I told her I said it. I bet my son looks better in a dress than you do
Do they cap?
Yeah, that was the only thing she agreed with me on
When I was live today
Well, how often do you go live?
You want to run bored?
I don't I'm not like I mean I used to do every day or
something like that hell you
I only picked up a couple of people from your
I stream every day this year. I hope for two days
Yeah
But I got I got C. So take care of during the day
So it's you know, and he's been real sick the last couple days
He's having extra fucking medicine so I have to kind of be alert
He's sleeping. He hasn't woke up at all today or tonight and he's usually up about anywhere from 3 to 4 30
And then he'll go back to bed
Are you are you nearby or he lives right above me?
His apartment is right above me. So my bed is right below his and it's a it's a stick built
Uh, so I can hit the two by fours cracking when he gets out of bed
That you're like alarm
I just let me know when he's up and I eat I have to pull two hours every night
With him. So if he's having a real bedtime, then that's when you don't see me at all. I'm upstairs
And I can't bite on the couch to make sure he gets his
His evening or his early morning meds because he takes meds like four or five times a day now
He's got a doctor's appointment in a couple of days, I guess
We might be looking at oxygen again, I don't know I don't know what they're gonna do he's going downhill for some reason
I don't know why
Hmm. He's only 66. Yeah. He's he just turned 66. I'm gonna be 60 in another fucking one
a week on the 16th. So, you're a uh a burgo or a burgo? I'm a burgo. I'm a burgo mercury
I'm in the hour and the day of mercury or some bullshit somebody did one of those
Sheets a long time ago on me and they said no wonder you're into
Medical into medicine and I went why's that she says you or nothing but mercury across the board and I went
What the fuck does that mean? She said medicals. That's all I know
Well, so what's your birthday? September 16th? Yeah, I was born in 115 in the morning
September 16th, okay. Yeah, I guess the time of day is important to the star
Yeah, it can be it can be important to the moon itself. Let's have a look it says
September 16th, okay, so I'm a book called the secret language of birthdays
Yeah, tell you a little bit about your day if you're you get me skeptical and everything, but just
Get me out. So it's better than the catch
Okay, that is the cars. Okay, so what are you on the right track? So I think it says the day of spirited energies
And it says, those born on September 16th display an indomitable spirit that does not
recognize defeat or boundaries.
Their desire to go beyond is a pathway that has already been done and any given area is
great.
Yet, they are patient enough to master the technical details of their craft, not being
egoist or wild-eyed fame hunters.
September 16th emotional energy is very strong, and it is from the heart that those born on
this day express themselves.
They must be aware, however, of overstepping certain boundaries, which even they must stop
and pause before with respect.
September 16th people are not afraid to just put it on the line.
are outstanding qualities, but because they rarely back down from confrontation, they
may often be at odds with the authorities or powers that be in their society.
Is that one of the 36 years in fucking probation?
Come in.
Copy.
Furthermore, they are by nature risk takers and must be aware of surrounding or coming
to the temptation of pure thrill-seeking for its own sake.
At some point, they have to reign in the rebelliousness of it.
It may be a mistake to cramp a September 16th person's style, but their spirit is so dynamic
that it will not be suppressed.
If you're just doing a child born on this day or attempt to break her or her spirit
will not succeed, and will certainly have bad consequences for all concerned.
Rather, the understanding parent should nurture and guide the spirit to move in creative
direction on its own momentum.
A careful line must always be drawn between orders and advice, forcing and leading, making
and allowing, take, killing and suggesting, etc.
September 16 people are filled with the zest for life.
Their competitive nature is promised, or is pronounced,
but their innate fairness usually rules out
underhanded dealings or win-and-all-cost attitude.
Those born in this day generally have to learn.
Had to be good team players.
Yeah, we're not good working with others.
Well, I always work independent.
Yeah, that was it.
I hope that was a nice little
Yeah
It hits pretty much to what I am. I am a feisty motherfucker. I will hit you
Without warning
I mean if I'm in a bar and somebody disrespects me, I'll look at it and say do it again
I'm gonna hit you and of course they're going to do it again
And therefore I'm going to hit you
Well, I'm gonna say thank you for posting
Who was it was I think it was my video or the trip his video, but of me
I like it. Yeah, I like it too. I was Willy Wonka. I was most I love you
You love Q. Oh, yeah, no I Q 45. I mean, yeah
or blogger blogger you I will always love blogger
He's my husband
What do you think about Alex mayors? She's a kind I'd like to hang her from the nearest oak tree
Okay, my god, okay, that is a little bit
You asked
Wait, okay, okay fair enough you asked that's a little bit a
little bit
I kept it short and sweet.
You don't like her though? I don't understand why you don't like her.
No, I think she's a backstabber, fucking cunt. She fucks with a kid.
Anybody that fucks with a kid or fucks with somebody's parents,
or fucks with their ex-wife, which she did with Blogger,
means that I'm ever coming near you.
I'm probably going to not be very pleasant.
I had to, if I could take a weak strike,
and fucking Trishalicious through Google.
And I took a week strike to peg them on my community page.
That channel is no longer in existence anymore,
so you can't look it up.
But yeah, fucking Trishalicious and fucking Alexander Mays
went after blog as child, ex-wife and kids offline
on the phone.
Trying to create havoc and blogger got a hold of me and he said do something about it old lady. So I did
And I shut them the fuck up that was last phone call bloggers family every guy
There's I will go to your house
You want to take it offline I'll bring it to you
No, a lot of people don't like that. That's where I got this tattoo. We was going to a fucking youtuber's house
It's she left the country. Would you like pull up on a Harley with like a big
Hold up in a brand new truck
Yeah, full-wit guys said truck I almost got paid off
I know you have guns and knives and stuff too, right? Who has guns knives and stuff. Yes, we do
I'm fully loaded. No, I've seen them. Like you can't show them
I watched an old episode and like Paige and you were like showing like pulling out huge knives and guns
I'm like knives are one thing, but you're not you're not going like this and saying bad things. You're just showing
The object and going well, I've got this well, she had that you know, I've got it's a collection I have
Being in that sword stuff like that. That's just showing off a collection. It's not
Threatening anybody with it. Yeah
There's the loophole with that, but if say if I always to pull out that
357 looking fucking BB gun and go like that
Then that's a problem, but if I said oh look at my new BB gun
Then it would
classified as just showing somebody something, but I wouldn't do it on U.S. anyways because
I have a little bit of morals that I just, you know, I don't go on channels that I don't
fucking like.
If I don't like you, I don't even watch your ass.
Why would I get aggravated at a piece of shit I don't like?
Well, yeah, we should I mean it's a I don't watch any even if I get pretty badly on the show
I don't usually go back to it. No, you do
No, I mean, I mean I'm beat as I would go back, but why why do you keep beating yourself over the head with that?
I won't anymore, but because she told me she's the one that she's told she finally says she doesn't want me there
So it's like I'm not gonna go back. She's that up 10 million fucking times, honey. No, she's always said I'm not going
She says she said I'm not playing over there
But she's like you can always come over here and she always like having that's what she wants
Well, it's fucking you to bring you and your crew so her numbers go up
But her numbers already are much better than mine anyway, so it's like I know that but the more the merrier and she's a greedy bitch
Plus she's narcissistic
So everything has to be on her terms or no terms at all
And I had I said that in like I'm like a video or something like that and she got so offended
It's like for you know, and I consider narcissists like extreme narcissists and like mild psychopaths are pretty soon the same
God definitely mild psychopaths. Yes
And it's like not saying that she's like evil or would she try to hurt people or anything
I'd say she
Believe if you were in her circle of friends and had not done what she asked to maintain the friendship
She would be in vengeance
Okay, yeah, okay
addictive
Just I played like a song about biscuits because she would like just keep teasing me with the word biscuit like in like post
Like tag me in post and play this biscuit song. So I made it. I made a song called like Persian biscuit
Yeah, and she's so mad about it that it's like
She can do anything she wants but if you turn around and try and fucking, you know, give her a little double indemnity
Then and then she gets asked for it
But it wasn't even like mean it wasn't huge
It just didn't show her in the light she wanted to be shown in and therefore her narcissistic ability fucking flared
Cuz she'll put me down to say calling me names like I know the name she was
God people were sending me clips they go and look and I'm like well
All you can do is fucking warn you and you wouldn't heed the morning when a lot of people like me
Back the fuck up off you
That should have been a sign.
That should have been a slap upside your fucking head
to go, whoa, wait a minute.
Why are the good people even
in all the fucking bitches and cunts staying?
There's a lot of weird things happening at the time
where I was like, Janet was there too?
And I was like, there was like, I was being targeted.
I was like off the air.
Yeah, but you were enjoying it.
I was I really was I didn't like the not nothing on it. I like I love me though
I mean, it's like I don't even care like you know, she's like has like a crazy personality sometimes
I love her but it's like she's just so mad at me
You can't be friends with somebody like that because you'll never live up to the expectations unless you're constantly kissing her ass
Yeah, and I'm not like and it's like, you know, I'm like
You are an ass kisser though. I mean
You'd like to appeal to people and you want to be liked and you will do
Why do you care if they hate you?
Well because I did have the show monetizing I wasn't pretty well on the show and now I've just been like so slandered that it's like
No one like likes me anymore seems like you do realize it's a fucking Tuesday morning
You fucking want a clock in the morning your time. It's four o'clock my time
Well, I mean I don't have that not that many people gonna be fucking awake because most people fucking work
I'm at work
I'm downstairs from Cecil's and I saw that you alive
I just pulled my two hours upstairs.
Ah, I just finished a beer.
I love you too, Mary. Hey, what's up, Mary?
Hey, Nancy, Mary. I know a lot of you guys.
I know, I know, it's like, this is late.
No, a lot of people are starting to get up on the east coast at four o'clock in the morning
So you can get out and be to work at seven
So they leave at six and get up at four have the coffee shit shower shave
Get presentable and go to work and leave by about six o'clock in the morning and get there for seven
There's a lot of New Englanders are up at this hour
The names in the chat are back to normal where it's like, you know, it used to be like their names that will come up.
No.
But back then you were making money from the fucking drama.
Well, I mean, I still, I'm making money and it's like, I mean, but it's just like, I had a great month last month,
but then like, then my people started harassing my donor because he's a guy and they're like, oh, you're gay.
And they took up all the drugs.
Yeah, you're gay and so what?
So what but he takes it personally and he is a straight guy and he like now he's embarrassed you know what you do like I do challenge just let him simmer in the chat because the more they're fucking down in you and shit like that in the chat.
Hey I picked on picks up on it on YouTube and says oh there's a lot of people in the chat.
They're actually talking and it benefits you even on all you have to do is ignore what they're saying
The chat won't handle itself
People will tell that motherfucker when they get sick of them to shut the fuck up
And that's what you got mods in the basement for okay
Chupac Shakur a fan channel I know you're KZ because nobody else likes KZ except himself
The second of all, he was very very obvious. He's a member not cool. Well, he was gifted a membership
He didn't buy a membership. He was gifted
so who cares if he's a member because I
Don't care, you know you the members like it really actually cares about the show. I've had a lot of trolls that are members unfortunately
So yeah
But you still got your fucking dear their almighty dollars, so
Yeah, this is like a little bit more stressful now, because I'm just bad timing and people think that I'm like some kind of spoiled or something like that.
Or you are.
You think I am?
Yeah, I think you're spoiled, bruh.
I don't agree with that because I think I work. I think I work very hard. I pay all I pay all my bills
I pay all my bills
All the bills yeah, and so I mean I do have some yeah, but you get a check
Not really a check I get up. Well, and that's like I have my apartment. Oh, Sam
I'm apartment and it's like I have to pretty much
Generate you don't
I'm doing it, you don't work except for handling a YouTube channel.
Right, but you know how much do you work a YouTube channel is a YouTube channel on YouTube for 14 years?
I'm fully in like the jobs, you know, you learn how to edit you have to learn how to these are all skills that you learn
That can be monetized to that you can help other people with
And and I've been monetized a couple times, but you know I well
I just edit for the shorts like I make these shorts that I've been pulling out of my
I doubt see I let a I do my shorts
Well, me too, but yeah, it's my shorts, but it's like I can only do a certain amount, but I've been doing like 20 a day for the past thing
Yeah, you know, I've been seeing it fucking rack my damn pages on recommendation when you do like 10 in a fucking row
I'm sorry. Oh, yeah, it's okay. It's all right. Hey, it's why I got the bell on so in case there's a good one
It comes across I can get a good chuckle
Sometimes they are
and
Yeah, well, I mean, I was interested to listen to my voice
Well, you have a nice voice
Please don't play my voice
Don't like it. I don't like to get myself. You're gonna love it. You're gonna love this book. No, I'm not
You can't tell me I'm a Virgo. I know what I like and what I don't
Well, this okay, this reminds me of you. Okay, okay
We go enjoy this this Tracy
Here we go.
P.B. Herman. He's dead now.
Oh, the old trucker. Yeah.
Thanks for stopping.
Some night on this very night.
10 years ago.
Along the same stretch of road
In a dense fog, just like this
I saw the worst accident I ever seen
There was this sound
Like a garbage truck
Dropped off the Empire State Building
And they finally pulled the driver's body from the twisted, burning brick.
It looked like this!
Yes, sir, that was the worst accident I ever seen.
God damn look at that old split window
God, I'd like to have that truck. Have a nice day
He sure and tell him large Mard sent ya
There you go, that's pretty good, huh? Yeah
I, uh, I can identify with this book when it looked like it was an international.
You want to say hi to Tracy?
Tricks is like going nuts.
Hey, Tricks.
How you doing?
Daddy's still paying attention to you and loving all over you.
It looks like.
Cute little kitty.
Yeah, he's basically saying you're minding of that actor. It's okay. That doesn't that's a good actor
That was a brief way. No, and then
I've been what's that one?
The hell she broke the guys. She hobbled him. Oh
So I agree with captain misery. Yeah, I've been I've had memes of misery made of me
Well, you know, I'm related to Kathy Bates. She's my like, she's my like eight cousin or something like that
We have a very
Grandfather those when the first US so you you've been in California all your life your family and shit
Yeah, I haven't actually I have my a family actually the city. I'm in right now, Redondo my grandparents were both born here
Redondo, and so yeah, my grandma my dad always is a oh you're it's helping with your six
California also in a Bishop, California, and like I saw a relative named Nevada because we have like
That is just right over the mountain range
I've never been in Nevada, I've never wanted to go to Vegas.
You ever want to go to Vegas?
No.
It's fun, but it's like, you know what, it's really cheap.
Because it's like all inexpensive because most people are just gambling and giving
much money to kids, you know what I'm saying?
So everything is like really nice.
There's one place in Nevada and and and Las Vegas that I want to go it's a place that does light shows
And they do concerts in there and it's really fucking cool
And they'll bring like the universe down on you and then all of a sudden fucking falling stars. I mean, it's it's elaborate
That would be the only thing that I could consider going to watch it
Sir, just a lay the bunny or someone says the bunny ranch
No, buddy, man. She doesn't exist anymore
that building exist anymore that the guy Paul died or
No, I guy that you stoned he's dead now
My gosh, mm-hmm. I happened to Air Force Amy. Have you heard of her? No
Well, she was she was like, you know, do you Eric the midget is or Eric the actor? No, I don't watch television
Well, he was on house. It was a radio show. But yeah, Howard Stern. I didn't like him
No, I didn't like how it's done
Yeah, he's just
He
His radio was like, it takes a fucking turn.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I just, I tried, I was more into what the hell?
They were on the lower East coast,
like from the Carolinas down.
And I can't think of his fucking name, but there was a red and they were more fun loving they didn't fucking ridicule people into fucking, you know, I just I don't get into that.
I'd rather get into something that's going to make me laugh instead of something that is going to bring out the fucking foul mouth in me.
You know, you know, I don't like it when I jump on the hate wagon.
Because I can be pretty fucking evil. Oh
Yon't tell me that
You're a sweetheart. I love you Tracy. You pissed me off
And then I fucking ran right for about I don't know maybe a week or two
And then I find that I'm not gonna get anywhere being pissed off about it
So why waste my fucking valuable time with it?
But I do get it off my chest
Well, because I don't want it to sit here and faster all the more because the more fastest the more I want to do
Something about it offline and the things that I dream about doing to some people. Yeah, I'm just totally not acceptable
Yeah
You do about like you're like that
Who's that movie with the rowdy rowdy pipers and those magical glasses and
Oh where he sees a certain shit sub subliminal messages. Yeah
Yeah, that was an old movie. I met Ronnie Ronnie Piper. I knew of him quite a lot him and rick flack
My mother-in-law was a manager at a gas station down the road from where those two had houses so they'd come there every morning
You know because it was you know, like a little convenience store, and then you had to pumps on either side of it
And they would come there every morning
So I would get like free tickets to wrestling matches backstage passes, and then I found out how
Fucking fake it was and I stopped going
I mean with the WWE I don't know what W it was
It was the first one whenever it was it was back in 1981 I was going to rest
Was it be a Christopher was born too that the year you graduate high school, I didn't graduate high school
I went and got a GED when I was 22
And I went to college
And then I left college and then I just started attending college just for accredited courses for certificates
Because I couldn't find I didn't want to go any farther than the medical field than what I meant. I
Tried an ambulance. I didn't like that
I tried hospital
emergency wards that
Jesus Christ who at times I wanted to throw up from what was coming flying through that door
The adrenaline was great
It was a hell of a diamond rush because you never knew what you're gonna see coming through out of that ambulance flying in the back door
So you were always in a rush to do shit. I tell you what the fastest work
I've ever had was working in an emergency room
And all I was doing was taking blood pressures and and shit like that and doing
Fucking sugar spikes where I'd break your fingers see what your sugar level was
No, I wouldn't allow do I could do insulin but I I can only do
Insulin for people at home that are dying
Like I can inject you with insulin, but I can't inject anything towards a vein
Because I'm I don't have a full bottomless license. You know summer
I know of summer
Summer has these like what the stuff to help something packs
It's like some kind of like shop. She is
Since impacts some facts. Oh, what are you heard of that? I've heard of the medicine, but I don't know what it's useful
You should see some of the medicines that sees was on the fucking it's got every fucking letter in the alphabet
It looks like when you go to try it
Thank God for AI because all I got to do is take a picture of the bottle and
It'll bring and then it'll lead me right to his chart and from there to lead me straight to his doctors in all of his
You know like kidney fucking, you know pulmonary fucking all the other doctors
He's got and that way I could fucking just do it all from AI
Trace you better than me, and I think you're better at me
I hated having to learn all that shit, but I can't put together a web page
Go I
Will do it for you. Yeah, I know but you know, I don't want to spend any money than what I do on I already spend what?
$23 a fucking month on family YouTube
Well, I mean family to be out. I wait until I got I got a deal
I think for like 13 or $14 a month for you. Yeah, cuz you're getting an individual
yeah
but uh
Yeah, I
Yeah, I try to get bad of all these other deals like it's a
See I got Cecil upstairs, so they made me get the other package and then they wanted me to pay they would charge me like 35
dollars
And I didn't have any at one point, you know, I was buying truck to fucking my dog was dying of cancer
I had medications and shit that was being done to him
So I told YouTube I says I can't afford fucking, you know, $37 a month to the family pack
And I canceled it and wasn't but a week later all of a sudden they said well, we'll give it to you for
A month for family pack and you don't lose any goodies and I went, okay, I can afford that I can afford it, you know
$25 but yep that extra $10. I just
Thanks junior for me and it's you were so expensive it
I know and they they when they doubled their fucking price
But if you cancel if you go to cancel stream yard, they'll offer you
$10 a month
Yeah, like much lower. Yeah, that's $10 a month. Yeah, why are you like me? I've got
I've got every email under Tracy Lee Moore, so it's Tracy Lee male hotmail fucking outlook
And all of all of my emails are the same
So, therefore, when it hooked up to that, it sucked in all of them, and it all leads
to my page.
So, when I want to use stream ads and my hours are done for the month, the 20 hours, then
I automatically, it'll log in under a different email and then it'll continue the free, you
know, because everything's tracially more.
Do you have AOL Dial-up?
Do you know this?
No, I wasn't.
No, I never had the money for that.
Only the rich people had AOL.
No, I was under...
Microsoft had an Outlook address,
and it was tracely more.
And then after that,
Yahoo came into it,
Then they were bombarding us. It was long before Google even fucking was well
It was being thought of but it hadn't come out on the market yet because AOL it was dominating
You know and I was working online when I first got my computer in the sex industry
Oh, you were in the oh, yeah, you were in the sex industry. Oh, oh, yeah
It's called
It was boy, I worked it is a boy or so and all I had to do is sit here fucking naked in most of the guys
You can't see them, but they can see you. It's just a one-sided fucking
visual
and ah
And they don't they they're they're jumping VPNs every fucking minute
It was jumping so they could never pinpoint where you were
so it was pretty safe and
Every week I got a fucking paycheck most of the time
I was sitting here talking guys about their wives and their kids and their jobs
And having a beer with them at 399 a minute
I was getting a
What was it? I think I was getting like $1.50 or almost $2, depending on how many hours
you could keep up a week for keeping a man on the phone wanting a bitch about his life.
And I worked at the bar anyway, so I was a prime candidate for it. I'd leave the bar
in my cut-offs, my fucking work boots, my bathing suit top, I'm working on the river
And they gets a fucking bed, drink beer, turn it on, and next thing you know, half the time, I was never naked.
Well, somebody made a profile on Instagram called Fish Chakos and Dick.
I had a picture of me and my feet was on it, between my legs down the head.
That's just troll love, that's all.
It's making you relevant.
I think they do love, they must love,
I think they must love me or something.
I don't know.
Even that or the closet in a quiz
that just haven't come out of the closet yet.
Yeah.
So they're mad at you because you live the life
that they wish they could.
No.
I think there's a few people like that,
like that are.
I think there's a lot of sexually frustrated
motherfuckers that have been hanging around you.
Oh my god, yeah, and say I can't help everyone figure out like what you saw like uh,
Yeah, but see there you go right there with that comment. I can't help everybody, but
See you're a nurturer. You want everybody to have everything and everything be kosher
And that's where you trip yourself up. You're too fucking
Wanting to help everybody else is to help in yourself, and then people take advantage of that niceness
That's true, but you're a very gullible motherfucker. Not gullible because I know
You're gullible, but I hardly get drunk anymore. I'm like really drunk
I kind of like that about you as I sit here and smoke a fucking left-handed cigarette
So for my little cars and you do one good you're having fun with it, and that's all that matters and you're learning I
Am I am learning all this shit besides fucking keeping up with the drama
Though you still got to tell me in the drama
Well, yeah, but I mean it's like I'm an Engoble. It implies to be like kind of simple
Engoble camp, you know, everybody's all I've got boy. It just means you're easily to be convinced you see that
Being nice to this person can get you brownie points or you know good attention
Then you're willing to take and accept the bad in the person just to get that kind of hair good that
might benefit you
Well, not benefit me, but it's like I want to I want
There's a person that I believe will come up and you're in the fucker
They're there and they're a lower self when they're coming to me usually I wanted to get their higher self
See where I'm the other side of that fucking it's like I'm the peanut butter
Yeah, and then you're the fucking sweet jelly that you know you put us together
We make a good fucking couple as far as you know friends
But there again, you're the sweet sucker that sticks to everybody and I'm the one over here going don't you touch me
Yeah
I
Might think I might think gum inside like the tootsie pop or I'm like, yeah
One two three and broke a tooth and then you can't eat the fucking camel
Poor owl
I don't remember that commercial as a kid.
I remember.
Well, you would have still remembered that commercial.
Because you were still watching Mr. Rogers and Sesame Street
when you were little, little.
Because Mr. Rogers and Sesame Street were the only,
like, I think we had them.
That was the only fucking channel that we could get out of.
There's nothing else on, like it was either like, you know,
there was like adult shows on all the networks.
No, remember Mary Happen, Mary Happen
when they pulled it off the fucking thing?
No, no you that way you weren't even thought of
Sorry, when they pulled it off. I remember you're see like on Sesame Street
They had like the Wicked Witch of the West did an episode and it was like too scary for everybody
Yeah, and they they fucking even pulled it from their line up. It's you see now
You can get the whole series of on online on YouTube
I think you get of all the sassama streets
and from the beginning to the end and that's they pulled like one or two of them so you can't even
they're like valuable episodes if you can find them such as the one the Wicked Wicked Wetches one
of them yeah and you watch that on youtube now they have moves but they have lost a few scenes
of it like there's a few like they didn't lose them they pulled them completely to where nobody
It's a liability thing
You know a kid get too scared and then somebody can you know a lot of people are so happy nowadays
I mean, we're scary episodes like the wiki-wish
She's like scary
When we're trying to get you to watch these programs so you can get repetitive fucking counting to ten
competitive
alphabet
colors shapes
That's what the adults were doing was what do you think it now like now that we have chat GBT
And you know that you know how parents would always help their kids
But sometimes they weren't as smart as the kids or they weren't able to help the kids as much as they wanted to right now
They are now they can just a chat GBT for the kids. I think what do you think about kids with chat?
I remember okay. This is where I have to go back and I'm gonna show my agent remember when calculators came out
Okay
And I live in New England, which is a fucking educational, fucking healthcare, uh, democratic state from hell.
And they figured if you came in with that calculator, they weren't allowed in school.
And if you did your homework, you had to write it out how you got to that number.
Next to the equation to show that you didn't fucking use the calculator to do it
Yeah, and then all of a sudden I got thrown out of fucking, you know
The property of all fucking schools in Massachusetts
So therefore I couldn't go to school because you know, I had a I don't know peace bond or whatever the fuck they call it and
Then all of a sudden kids got to bring them to fucking school
Yeah, and I'm like you motherfuckers. I would have been so fucking good at math because I liked math
Yeah, had I been able to do that and I probably would have become an architect instead of going into the health field
So
Well, I think everything happens for a reason we go to like where we're led sometimes and I can't stand blood
Oh, I can't stand blood
oh somebody's got your fucking blood if I don't see it and instantly respond to it to stop it
but if somebody walks up to me and says look I like it weak in the knees I do
that's why I never went any farther with the fucking the hell shit I just ate the certificates
G tube j-tubes fucking, um
You know DHS is I think it's the is it DMS
Digital digital
Ractal stimulation. They want an extra three hundred three dollars. I got a paper from the fucking state
They said if I was doing a g-tube or a j-tube which are feeding tubes
Okay, or, um, a fucking digital rectal stimulation, then they would pay me $3.50 more an hour.
But I had to prove that I was doing one of the three to my client in order to get it.
Which was fucking crazy. I read the paper. I thought they wanted money more taxes
So I wouldn't open the fucking thing until I had some money
I turned around and opened it online and that was the first thing it said was
The IRS and I'm like, no, I don't think I need your extra $3.25 an hour
Yeah, I don't think she should let me do that
Oh, let me just untangle my, I have my uh, my light, I'll tangle it with my stuff. Hold on. Okay.
You're falling apart. I am falling apart. You're falling apart. Put your trap together, man.
It's not working. Oh, hold on. Oh, if I can't do it, 44.
Like almost I felt almost like I'm 45 now, you know
Yeah, I'm a yeah, I feel like I feel like it's I'm going really fast and uh, yeah
Yeah
Days are starting to speed up on you
Yeah, it's the life is like I miss my dad a lot, you know, it's like yeah, yeah
My dad lived in California
gave away a house in California oh my gosh they're probably be worth a lot
today huh probably but I don't give a fuck and it was it was locked in at 900
and $460 a month HOA too and I gave that one fuck away that's how much I hate
California well you know I'm in California because of my family and then
it's like but since my dad passed away I'm not sure how much my family was
Much to do with me, but
Well
You know that you always be in touch with them because you are who you are
Yeah, well right now I'm right next to everybody, but I'm like
You self on YouTube a lot though. Yeah, but I think my dad was the only one that really wanted me here
And he would like really make it up for you the Gemini
Your dad loved you
And
At least you had that
I did I did
You had a good upbringing
My mom is great to you and I love my mom
But you were daddy's guy. Yeah, I
Didn't love his kids. He loved all his kids. You could tell you're not a mama's boy. That's something. I
Really like about you. You're not a mama's boy. You're you know
Well my mom's a cancer and I'm a capricorn they're opposites they're opposites on the wheel
Like we're a complete opposite to like she's very sensitive and crabby and I'm my mother's a fucking Taurus
Oh, wow
Yeah
That bitch had a hell of a right hook. I
Know because I was like I was like, you know, I was like, oh
Taurus is rule by Venus, but it's so it's like a lot of love and beauty and
And oh, yeah, and they're very dear tourists. I find to be very
Once they get with one person
That they're they committed there there is loyal dogs
Virgos are pretty loyal dogs until we get hurt.
You hurt us and we don't give a fuck about you anymore.
You don't have a name anymore.
But I also think Virgos, it's like they say,
they say the virgin very ironically.
See my brother was a Virgo growing up.
There's three years, four days difference
between I'm the 16th, he's the 20th.
So we thought alike.
I mean, we were like fucking mutton Jeff.
You know, I mean
Yeah, you're the same side
Oh, yeah, we we were fucking right on
Do you know what do I Alexander and I get along like I think so well
Because she's kissing your ass right now watch out. She's gonna stab you in the back
You're the same birthday. You're the same exact with what you understand that but I'm just saying that
She does she says in the back
I'm not going to say I told you so. No, no, no, but I don't think she will I think I know she will she can't help it
She's the vindictive side of what you are. I think if she was if she was to it would be
Say something bad about it do something all I had to do to piss her off
met her like 18 hours 18 hours after that I talked to her online on her fucking
piano or something like that and we clicked just like you and her did right
And this is my experience. This is way before blog or any of that bullshit. It was just you know, and uh
Reclicked and she wanted to go to Salem for new um
For October 31st, and I said well hell I'm right down the fucking road. I'm about 70 miles from Salem
Let's clap. Do you want to listen with me wishy stuff?
Well, no, she won't she wanted to collab with somebody in Salem, you know
It's gonna be a witchy right it's gonna be pretty witchy, right?
I don't go to Salem. I believe in God. I know
No, they didn't see their furtans, but the thing is what I'm getting to is the next morning Tommy was on
And I used to love Tommy till he pulled that shit that he pulled with clumsy
No, with fucking scummy that was dirty pool right there. I'm kind of I'm mad at Tommy
Yeah, I'm mad at him
I have every right to because I fucking liked Tommy a lot I
Had a lot of respect for that drug addict. You know what I mean?
But after what he did to clumsy that was fucking dirty pool
Well, what do you think about the beta stuff? Have you heard about like what beta said about clumsy and stuff?
She's just doing in the bandwagon and anybody she can hate she goes in circles if you look
She'll start with one and then she'll keep going around and around and around and then she'll come back
She'll give everybody, you know a break because she's attacking somebody else
She feeds off of whatever's going on in chat.
If somebody's talking bad about somebody like that or somebody comes up on the panel
and says something off the wall about them.
automatically she says well I used to like them or I think I like them and
then they'll browbeat somebody and then in the next sentence she's already
flipped because she knew that she's got another 15 minutes of people fucking
screaming hollering and brow beating somebody and that's not cool though is
You want me to be fucking nice until we fuck each other
Shit's gonna have to fuck a fan and
and
You need to make fucking nice for people, but there's some people you just can't make nice
And why try with I try with beta and I know you did I know you two were such close friends
And it really hurts me to see that she was such a cunt
She was bossy and she she's narcissistic. We all know this and we accepted her for it
But now she's become spiteful like every fucking word that comes out of her mouth
It's like she's spitting nails at you
Yeah, I
Can't do that
And I can't I mean she was yeah, she'll say like she'll she will say oh he will he's nice to his cats
But then she'll say like oh, he's a griptur. He's like a oh
She'll say, oh, he's nice to his cats.
And then the next sentence, she'll
talk about your floor when it was a table.
Yeah, it was actually the table.
I know it was the table.
I saw the video.
And I'm like, that's a fucking table with asses, fucking
widows, and fucking just party supplies
that had been taken and used up.
Yeah
People will say oh, they thought it was shit. They're like, oh my god. They're shit on the floor
Oh, that was a table. Oh, yeah, we eat the tobacco and the weed
Yeah, they get into it it's like cat nap
Yeah, but no no, but my cats don't like I mean
I've never seen them ever get it the catnip has like a scent that like they can smell from a mile away
Yeah, my cat doesn't touch my wheat oh
Budweiser never touched my fucking beer on all my weedles. You never drink your Budweiser's
See I got him from a pill fucking distributor up there and he just break falls from on right
And um, he come running through and she's like, yo motherfucker, he was chasing the cat and then I saw the cage that she had him in.
And she lives in a house, all she had to do was open her back door to let him go to the bathroom instead.
She made him shit in the rabbit cage and explained to him, sleeping it.
And I saw him go by me and I said, how much for the dog?
While I was getting my other party supplies from her right and um, she was 300 dollars
I said I'll be right back. I took my belt off
I handed her what I ordered for the party supplies
$300 for the fucking dog and I grabbed my belt to put around the dog's neck and I said you're no longer, buddy
Your name is Budweiser. Let's go get a beer
and
Yeah
That was it. He was my best friend. He's still up there in the bag. I can't even touch the fucking bag
My mom is my grandma my grandfather thinking the ashes on somewhere
She's like, oh, I got fucking dead people on the other side
I got fucking a friend and they died right and then to another friend Papa Phil had ashes of fucking Norman
I had an ashes Norman. So when Papa Phil died, I got fucking Norman's ashes
I'm gonna dump them in the river and we'll go over there without having to pow out this year
Every year on the river the fucking engines get together and have pow out and I go to it
And they dump
They're gonna dump Budweiser and Norman Gilmore in the fucking river. They're the only ones that can legally do it instead of Massachusetts
They can get rid of fucking ashes anywhere they choose because they're fucking engines, you know
They're native that this is their fucking land
We just fucking buy it and pay the taxes on it. They don't have to pay taxes or nothing. Yeah, nothing
Any Indian they lived in a state of Massachusetts
They get pretty much everything free as it should be because you know us Europeans were really fucking mean
The horses were dogs
I don't know no horses were already here
There were if the Aztecs up there were dogs
Uh, I don't know about the Aztecs don't live down to fuck itself
So the pride of fucking this continent. I live up in the higher end
I'm closer to greenland than I am to fucking Mexico
Did you see Crystal Marie on the show last night at all?
I caught your little blips and let me see there was somebody else that made that that's another one
God damn any man get with that woman you got your hands full
Yes, you do I I'd be praying for you brothers
And thank you Tracy I do
Because Chris DeMarie, I have no problem with her.
But the shit that she's deep into the offline bullshit.
And she has no problem telling people about it.
If she sees something or hears something that ain't right on the flip side of the fucking YouTube coin.
You come on, fuck, tell everybody about it.
Well, yeah, but she, I mean, good times told her about it.
Like, good times said, oh, yeah, my grandmother, you know, was robbed and murdered by somebody.
And then she was, like, on a show saying, good times murdered her, unlike his grandmother
and stuff.
But it wasn't a hint.
It was, like, somebody else.
I mean, it's, like, so she gets confused a little bit.
I don't know.
She's a drinker, ain't she?
Yeah, yeah, she's a drinker. She's uh, I don't want to call her drunk, but
She's uh when she's on YouTube. She's usually smashed
It's what all the adults do we can't afford to go to the bars and during COVID
They shut down everything and everybody lost their businesses. So there's no there was fucking seven bars around here
There's only one it's a riding gun call
All right
No, there's only one gay bar.
No, we use YouTube.
I'm a gay bar.
I can go to sports bars right now.
You don't want to?
There's no gay bars?
There's one gay bar in, like, the five-city radius.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, that's sad.
There's one gay bar, and I think it's in there as well.
You know, I would think that they would have more gay bars.
They do in some cities, but not in this one
Yours are more working up in the society
You mostly the people that live that are
Owned of something live there full-time. It's a straight city. It's very straight. It's very
It's good, you know
No much for hate crimes, then
Not really. There's not really hate crimes, but you know, it's like
Yeah, but look where you're at. I mean, I'm in the middle of fucking boondocks covered with fucking pine trees
And you could walk to the beach
You can see the the fucking, you know, what is it sunrise?
I bet it's beautiful
I mean, I would I ever go to California? Oh
It would take somebody really him
somebody I like
And I had the accommodations all set up. Yes, if it was you I would come see you
Thank you. Yeah, I really would because
You and I can talk like normal people because I don't bring up
And therefore, we can have
conversations about other things.
Right.
Like we're having right now.
Imagine if we were just talking about, like, six, or six months ago in our fight, does
that help?
Imagine if it was Joe up here?
Oh, my gosh, yeah.
Joe's a lot of energy.
I love Joe.
Joe loves me.
He is a definition of a prick.
It would have a picture of Joe right next to it in a dictionary
Yeah, he can fucking ruin a fucking panel in a heartbeat and he sits back and laughs when he does it
And I just sit back and laugh
I mean sometimes but it's like sometimes not very fun. I know yeah, it's not something
But that's when it's the funniest because he does it anyways
He has no limitations to his mouth, and that's why I love him
You know
Yeah, I mean it yes, but at times it is
Unappropriate and then he kind of swallows and kind of kicks it back a couple of years
But yeah, I I love Joe
And he's good at it
Well, I have one song before we go because I think the chat's kind of falling asleep with me
Oh, you gonna jump off?
But yeah, but I'm gonna play a song before I go. This is like a troll-side of the panel, this is based on at least a Geordana song
Oh, I like that, bro.
Here we go. You too.
I feel like I've been locked out
Spend my soul in a way. I shouldn't have thought out. I'm still following Betty Manson real close to
He I've been falling
Back when Lisa was fucking hanging with him
Uh-huh.
That's a cute picture.
This has a song called
Darks to the City.
This is called Trollside of the Panel.
Play it.
I'm trying to like it.
My Tupac's wondering what I know about Massachusetts?
Oh, I do know a lot.
Yeah, I do know a lot about Massachusetts.
But people that I know a lot about Massachusetts are dead now.
If they're dying now.
But back in the 70s,
Hot damn it, there's a lot of drugs and money made around here.
A lot of fucking Italians.
Whoa, look at that, look at that white belly.
Jesus Christ.
I, I, I, I lift weights.
I gotta keep my tits in check.
I do, I got a bar, a couple barbells I lift weights.
In the morning
I had some drunk up
What are they
All that
No, I did that
And I fucking bought a six-pack and I drank them all and I was still thirsty
And I was fucking humming and I went to grab that seventh one
All of a sudden I had the worst fucking heartburn I could I'll never drink that shit again
I'll stick if I'm gonna drink something like that. I get vodka and then
vodka goes with everything
Yeah, it looks like it's like in Russia. They call vodka water
Well, yeah, cuz the most of the water was no good
Tell me the fucking motorcycles Tracy have you met Mason?
Huh, have you met someone named Mason?
Mason, yeah, are you there? It's Santa Tracy. Yeah, what's up? Hi, what you doing darling?
Hey, uh, psych like who's who's that that you're with like your friend. Yeah my friend Tracy. Yeah
Nobody's right. Yeah, wait site. So are y'all actually together or what?
No, wait a minute, you're gay. We can't miss to Jesus because you say me just my son. I'm not fucking dating you
Hey, well, the Tracy Mason is in a group. He's in a group home and he's like a very sweet person
That's cool. That's why I'm kind of keeping it. Oh, I know just his voice was a little different
It's like so you're actually pretty good with that person that there's with us
Yeah, of course. I'm a good person
Mason Mason's always ready to date me Tracy. He's never been in it never dated a guy, but
You think no
They said she said we can't date anymore. I'm sorry
Sikes like you want to be with but is that a woman that's like is that a woman that you're with like on here? Yeah
I live in New England. It's cold. We wear fucking
hoodies in the water
It's like 50 degrees out there
It's like, so what do you want to do from this point on?
Well, what do you think?
Mason, are you to come out and visit me
and sleep in the bed with me?
Like, you promise?
I thought that was something that you wanted, though,
psych.
Right, I do, yeah.
Yeah, so you gotta, it's like,
it's gotta cover your way someday.
You, are you gonna, are you gonna fly over here?
Are you gonna come my way?
Are you gonna go my way?
It's like
It's okay, how about you just take Tracy and leave me out? No, no, no, no, I'm already taking them bloggers
Okay, so I could psych who is she actually which is what somebody?
He's with blogger. Yeah, well, I can't I can't be with anybody. I am strictly bloggers
No, that would mean he can cheat all he wants, but I I don't
It's like what do you want to do here, man? What do you think is good?
We just make out for like 20 minutes and then see how you like it from there
And then you can like say yes or no, that's that that's what you would like those psych
That's what you want to do. Yeah
Not coffee
Go straight to the make it out first. Take your Starbucks and then there you go. You're frappuccino, baby
Frappuccino. Yeah, he's got to have his frappuccino on this day
That's the way it's gonna be like right well, I mean if you don't want to I'm not gonna like
Yeah, no force in there. I'm not gonna force you. I'm not gonna force you
I'm just gonna like say I'll be in my on my bed and you can just come the offers often
No, it's like I don't mind. No, it's like I don't mind be like with you like to hang out
But I mean, I don't know if I should go any further though
You don't know. Well, so maybe you should
Yeah, but it's like it's hard to know because I never bit through that
Yeah, try to know right
Huh if you try it with me to know if you like it, right?
You mean we got a test it out psych see what happens
Don't say it's right. I was fixin open my mouth, but that would have been mean
I am I'm sitting over here. Just smoking my fucking left-handed cigarette
It's okay, Mason, you know, find a nice girl, but Mason, just forget about me, okay, Mason?
Yeah, you should forget about me.
I'm too old for you.
I'm too old, and it's like, you're too good for me, you're too, you're too, you're too
like of a nice person.
Really?
Psychic would have been mental abuse.
Yeah.
I'm a bad person.
Mason, you know what I mean?
Yeah, so I got that you I thought you're a nice person like I'm a nice person, man. No
No, when it comes to emotions
Psycho's too needy
You drain you
Flight
Hey, so I guess who I like so I guess who assault today
I saw Sponky. I want the Sponky's thing today or what the Sponky was like on today. She's live
I saw you there and remember what happened in Sponky's last night when she was making fun of me and then I left in a huff
No, but she was on live today though, Sike
Lesson 12 hours ago and she was so mean to me
Wait, what happened site? Never mind never mind. Just be friends. She's cool
I think she's over me and everything she just thought was so funny to me
But it's okay
Mason you can go where you want if you think you go to go to Sarah's kiddies channel to
Sarah's kiddies on this guy
No, no, it's like like what happened. I mean you weren't there today though when I was on her uh
When I was on spongebob today, you weren't there
Remember she she made fun of me last night. I said I was never coming back again
Wait, you're never gonna go back to our tour again
It's like what did you say not a less what apologize I was laughing stock of YouTube
Huh? I was laughing stock of YouTube. What does that mean?
Like what does that mean?
Everyone just thought it was a joke and
It's one of my cut of me
So she doesn't want you to come back psych or what happened?
I don't think so because she put a picture of me the gaudy made for like a minute on full screen on the chat
And it was embarrassing and then
No, no, but no, but it's like the thing I didn't understand is like when I went back to you know
Go on there after I left her stream and I came back on the same day today
She said the second time I came she said the second time I was trying to come on today
She didn't want me to come back on because she said she had enough for me
She was she had enough for me like today
Hey, Christine come on up Christine. Come on. Can you come up?
You know Christine you Christina Tracy and Mason. I don't know
I've never heard of that person, Scythe.
Well, hopefully she comes up, she's awesome.
She's a nurse, she has a little dog named Fawzi.
You're really cute.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah.
No, wait.
No, wait, Syke, why would Sponky let me on her stream today, but then when I came back again later on, she said, no, we had enough for me today.
Did you make her mad? You said something that she didn't like or something?
No, I didn't say anything wrong, Syke. I didn't make her mad or anything like that, so I don't understand.
Maybe because you know what she has some people around her that are just like kind of like mean people and I don't know
Maybe they told her not to let you on or something. I don't know
I would always let you on me soon. You never did anything wrong here. You're always good
No, no, but psych I didn't do it like all I did was just go to talk to her and that's all I did
I talked normal to I never said anything wrong or anything you asked her to take off her top or something
No, I was just asking her about her being like my you know with me stuff like that
I think that might have made her feel that way. Yeah, no she doesn't want to she has a boyfriend named Justin
She doesn't want to like talk about. So she doesn't want to date any other guys, right?
And she also doesn't want to upset me because she knows you're my boyfriend, right?
Huh?
She knows you're my boyfriend, right? I thought I thought we weren't I thought we were just friends
Yeah, I thought you already figured that one
It's like you and I were friends
No, I don't have any friends
I just have a boyfriend and I have you know female friends, but guys are gonna
No, but no, but like I didn't say no nice like I didn't really go that far with the spunky today
I don't know. I don't know. Spunky, maybe he's in a little bit of a spunky mood, but, you know.
Are you going to let that person up, though? You said there's a person that's going to come up.
Who is it? See, who's coming up? I think that's Christine. Christine, come up.
You said there's somebody else? You told me that there's somebody else coming up.
Christine might come up. I don't know if she will, but I hope she does. I'm gonna say hi to her
Okay, well, I'm getting too drunk right now to like I know it's five o'clock in the morning here
Yeah, well, I love you guys. Hey, I love you Tracy. Thank you
Yeah
So Mason
So what did you want to tell me? I want to tell you I'm freezing cold right now
I'm in my bed shivering on the covers
Can you fly?
You're saying that you need me to help you with that or something. I do. I need you to help warm me up
Can you come warm me up under the covers?
You want me to warm me up psych or what? Yeah, we can do that
If that's I mean, that's that's what you want man. It's exactly what I want. Oh, it's like that's what you want, right?
Okay, okay. Yeah
Okay, well Mason we're doing one step at a time, you know, I'm not gonna pressure you or anything
I know it's a little bit weird
But you know what? Yeah, but yeah, but like we didn't know like we didn't really get that far with each other yet
We're only we only knew each other for like a short amount of time. I think I
No, so it's gonna be like a baseball game for so many to first base and then I'm gonna second base
I'm gonna third base and then we're gonna do a home run
Yeah, but that'll take steps though. Yeah, like you're talking about right
Baseball games are very very long games. I mean they're very boring, but you know what no, we're gonna have a 70 stretch
You believe what's happened that?
Hey site, so where's um, where's Sebastian at then he never came to see you?
No, Sebastian or you're here in the chat. Hello, Sebastian. You did you have a crush on spunky?
I thought she was cool and stuff like that psych, but I don't know
Well, what is this monkey said? Oh instead of going to psyche's house and in his bed
She's like, why don't you come come here? It's monkey's house
No, it's like I told her no psych
I told her that I come to yours and also go to hers, but she I don't know what happened
Well, that means what you blocked you shouldn't one of your
No, no, it's like she didn't no site. She didn't block me. She just said uh
She only won me on there one time. She didn't want me to come back after the second time I came back on
Well, I have to have a talk with her about that because you know what no one's gonna pick on my boyfriend
Okay, no, so it's like I so it's like you got me, right? I'm the one that's with you. Yeah, we're together
Is that okay with you like so we're like so we're together like right?
Mm-hmm
Yeah, yeah, yes, like that's okay, man. Okay
Well guys, what's like?
So I got a heart what are you gonna do like about what she's saying to me though? You're gonna try you're gonna try to talk to her
I'll have a talk with her. I'll let's talk with her
We have to boil the mud wrestle with her. I'm gonna do it and I'm gonna let her know
Don't talk with my man. Okay. It's like yeah
Yes, like it doesn't make sense why she would be that way when oh she wasn't like that the first time I went on there today
You know next time I went on there. She acted a different or little strange
Isn't that so typical of you know, some people like they'll have a different personality. You know what I'll always be the same
It's like I think she has a split personality or something like that right my polar disorder or something
Like there's something not right, right? So like there's something awful about her. Yeah. Yeah. I felt the same
I feel the same way. I'm just it's funky. I love it. I'm just good
You know what? Smunky's a nice person, but she does have a boyfriend and sometimes when you have a boyfriend you're like
Another guys hit on me. Is she just being like is she just being cautious because she has a boyfriend that's all yeah
I think so. I think I think she's like trying not to get just in two jobs
She's not trying to go like for she doesn't want to get in trouble by going with another guy if she had
Imagine her boys were in the locker in the house and not let her ever leave again
Yeah, do something. No, but no, but site it's funky even told me that she likes me being on her
She told me that I'm her, you know, cool with her, but I don't know what happened
Well, you know what there's sometimes there's mean people there too, like it was got you there
Or he's me or it's JT and it was rain there rain probably did it was play rain. It's like, oh, don't let uh
No dingle. No dingle was in there site. No dingle was in there. Dingles nice. Dingles like the little cute penguin
Yeah, that's it. Yeah, Christine. Why are you being like that Christine? Stop it. No. Are you being like Christine?
No
This is being weird
Yeah, wait so I can see in your back chat or worse. She though on her panel
She's in a regular chat asking me to take take away her all her like power. I'm not going to do it because why?
The first time you've been here weeks and then you're mad at me for what I do you
Like so you want me to
It's like so you want me to warm me up man. Get you like warmer. So you won't be cold
Yeah, can you do that? What wouldn't you want me to do that though site? Well, how soon do you get here?
Well, I don't know what wouldn't you want me to be there?
I mean now you get over here right now. It takes time for that though site
Just for a while like not too long
Several years
No, not years like maybe like a couple like couple like a
Couple months right or something
Well, who do you have that? Who do you have to go through to get your plane ticket to come?
Who's gonna get I just got a fun
It's like I got to find a way man. That's all I can do is find a way
Guys, it's someone contact
Mason, he's my boyfriend contact Mason and say you want to help him get here
All you have to do is pay for his plane ticket and probably like a team of
Specialists to make sure he doesn't get lost
And it's like so you never know like it it might come sooner than you think is it's got it's just a matter of
Getting it all together for me to be able to make that happen
I know I know. Hey, do you know Mr. Big Pipes?
Huh?
Do you know Mr. Big Pipes?
No, I never heard of that. Who's that?
Sup brother
Mr. Big Pipes
Trying to show so psych psych this the person you're talking about with us
What's your big pipes?
I never heard it. I never heard of such person site
You know why he's called that? You know why he's given that name?
What why why?
He's a huge dick. Holy shit. What happened? Wait say it again. Never mind. Like say it again. Holy crow
He's a big he's a big I was at a bagpipes
How do you know that a big set of bagpipes? Yeah?
But how are you so I mean I agree like statistically
Have a picture of it. Yeah, you could throw it in the AI you could throw in the AI and be like I can't show it
Can I show up mr. Reprise or no? Yeah, yeah go for it. Yeah, okay
Why why do you want to why do you want to do that because you said yes, I can't I mean I don't really like it's not necessary
But I can you said it's okay. No, you can
Leave me for you
So it's like what happened
Mr.. Big Pipe sent me a picture of his dick
It's like why would you leave me for somebody else? I thought you wanted me. I'm not going. I was just kidding
Wait has this guy sent you a picture of his dick or Mason or you send me a picture of it?
I asked him to he's having some drumming and then I've never got a chair. I've never got a chance to say
Well someday mine's really bigger. So I can't well, it's a bit of your luck. I can't find your picture right now
So I would just imagine a very large
Sike, so you're going for him instead of me. Why would you go?
No, mr. Big Pipes isn't my type
So big pipes. I'm sorry. I'm I'm with me now, okay
Mr. Big Pipes, yo
I'm in love with Mason now
Go for it, dude
Hey, Mason, do you want to have a threesome with mr. Big Pipes in me?
It's like it's like I don't know what to do man like
There has to be a chicken
It's like you have somebody else in here with you, so I don't know.
That's your only chance, but it is a chicken ball.
Christine, Christine, can you help me out?
Christine, can you take one for the tear?
Distract Mr. Big Pipes while me and Mason, like, what?
I'm sorry.
I'm not funny.
Guys, I'm sorry.
Oh, Mr. Big Pipes, talk to me.
I have to go soon, but just keep talking.
It's so funny.
Hucked a mace
Well, I got another crypto donation. What the frick one. Let's see how much it was
It's like a dollar or a four, dude. Let's go back. So how far back how far back do you go with the mr. Big Pipes?
Well, we dated in like that in like 94 90s 396 every fucking digital
That's how far back you go psych with
We were born in the same hospital the same day.
Really?
Yeah.
It's like you're serious about that?
Yeah, like Mount Sinai.
Sinai.
Yeah, at a dream we're at the Mayo Clinic.
And we're very professional.
Okay.
You know what?
Mr. Big Pipes and Mason.
Separated at birth and now he wants to like reconnect.
Well, Alexander said that she thinks we're very similar people. Hey, man, how are you?
Do you think we're similar mr. Blue pipes?
It's like where's your cat at man? Oh, no
You shred like nasty jazz licks and shit
Dude, I shred NASA. Yeah, I was playing the nastiest shit like the last like 30 minutes from my stream
I just fucking got nasty
Like playing just okay. Seiki is delusional with psychosis induced
My alcohol drugs and trauma never repaired
You okay?
Your alcohol and drugs and trauma in a repair. I didn't think you overdo that. I'm kind of out of alcohol
I don't want to drink anymore. I had four but I says talk in
Christine by the way, Christine. I have to ask Christina question. Oh Mason left. She's not asking question. Christine
This is really shocking. I just need to make sure it's Christine
There's some allegations made last night, and I want you to address it. Okay, you can come on panel
if you want to but
I mean, I want you to really address what Crystal Marie was accusing you of.
Did you see that, Mr. W-wait, what did Crystal Marie was saying?
Guys, did you see this?
Watch this, Mr. W-watch this, Mr. W-this is shocking, um, shocking developments.
This is what Crystal Marie has figured out, everything, okay?
Watch it.
I don't know.
Oh.
Oh, you-no, bring it back, bring it back.
You you fucked it up, buddy
You gotta switch the screens
There you go there
That's you
We're just gonna break it
And you know like that first thing I told you these people like that fucking I told you like that the same people or
Like you wouldn't even believe that their age, you know what I mean? It's like
Well, I'm saying that that I wouldn't understand that a bitch
That would act like that like that is like I guess she's like a lot of criminal record and she's trying to cover it up
So
We're just gonna break it
Christine that we not the Christian we all know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, she's got a big criminal record. She's got to get fucked
Aaron got friends
No, no, no, yeah
Why what you do?
Do you see the Camille? Yeah, she's a bad criminal
But she do
She kills kids. Oh my god, please. Oh, no, no, no, no
Christina are you there? Yes. I'm here. Christine. What is that about? Oh, let me tell you what that is about
How dare you how fucking dare you you don't see me going other channels
Talking shit about you, but you have a delusional fucking drunk up there
Stay in that shit about me and then yours. Oh, no, not our Christine and then oh, she's a nurse
Fuck you psych fuck you
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, you don't get to make excuses. I said he's had here and I've watched
the bullshit you've been doing and I've not said bullshit to you or about you at any of these other chats.
You can go straight to hell and you keep your little drunks and your little druggies and your little
polls in your chat because
People like me that have supported you for all these months will never support you again ever
Okay, well, why are you so mad why?
Well, you know something you made yourself look dumb
Don't make excuses don't make excuses do not make excuses
You've been going after everybody saying they're threatening you they're saying bad things about you and you're a fucking drunk up here
talking about faggots and Christine killed kids and and you said she said I listen to its site
you can go to you can go to the tree is talking about do you understand me
she's talking about the tree of us slurs
Yeah, I don't know. I thought it was like, you know, I was like letting Crystal look ridiculous because I thought she looked weird and I thought nobody like believed it, but it's like, Christine obviously took it.
Well, I can't tell if it comes out of her mouth, you know? I was like, actually, I was literally talking because it makes her look weird.
Burping so much, sir.
Do you mad at me? I didn't say shit. Why do you mad at me for people saying stuff?
It's like am I supposed to mad at people saying so and be this channel about me like which they do all day
And how I'm just like this trash human being and that was gross. It was gross on me
He's scared with Mason and I think I will take away her lunch because she doesn't seem very nice tonight
know I know it's the guys it was like Mike O'Rourke. Oh, she might go rogue. Oh, please.
But everyone already went rogue. Hits gum and other people. Christine! Christine!
I mean, see, I was on your side. I don't know about now and now I'm on Crystal's side.
Oh, please. Christine!
I told her it was the car that did it.
I didn't say it was her car, I don't know that lady.
I remember being really mean to me one time.
I don't get, guys, can anyone control Crystal's mouth?
I don't know what you were saying.
All I know is that it was a funny fucking-
You're not, oh, Crystal or he's always mean to me.
But the Crystal lady is like really mean to me.
Yeah, I will, I will, I will, Crystal,
because you've gotten nuts, Crystal.
Oh shit, that's so loud.
But the car is named Christine, that's what Christine is saying about this killer car.
But no, but that's...
That's not like a dodge.
No, what kind of car is that?
I feel like I knew that trivia.
Christine, don't get mad at me.
Christine, it was funny to me because it was so off the wall.
Not believable, but it's like I don't you think it was something that believable. I don't think it was
I think it was just like obviously like ooh
Plymouth fury a 1958 Plymouth fury
Christine the killer car was even King novel right? Hey, that's probably the year she was born in 1958, right?
Like they're born the same year
Right, that's why she's actually named after the car Christine. I mean she is she really yes. Yes. She's she's born in 58
I don't know. I don't I don't care what you hear. I love the lady the car and Christine
58 points fairy go over man a crystal Christine
She's like she's trying to get crystals young blood
She's trying to, like, she needs, like, she's trying to get
Crystal Marie to sacrifice herself.
If anyone's a vampire, it's Crystal Marie. Crystal Marie is probably, like, 500 years old.
That's something to look natural.
Yeah, she definitely had some, like,
I think she got the suction shit done.
Christine, Christine, Christine.
Pumped into her lips.
Christine, are you okay? Christine, hold on.
Christine, the chat. Are you okay, Christine?
How is the car named Christine and a nurse fuck me second okay because you always said you were named after the car
Christine right and
He said you're a nurse like I don't know. I don't know why you're like
I'm right. It's also from my panel. Okay
Well, I know I am but I was like I was actually thought it was kind of funny
Which because he was saying ridiculous things and or obviously not true
It's like things are said about me that are obviously not true. I get mad too. I understand where you're going, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you're saying, but I don't know what you
Yeah, isn't it funny, Christine?
Isn't it funny?
I was just on it.
My best friend is Spunky, you know, was saying it too, or like, you know, laughing about it,
you know?
I mean, obviously I'm getting that upset.
Christine, obviously it's not true.
So why would I get upset about it?
Like, that upset.
I mean, it was annoying at first, but it's like, it's obviously not true.
I'm not going to be offended.
It's just some idiot.
Christine, you know where the communities are coming from.
All right, Christine.
Okay, let's look at let's turn against each other person. Let's turn against each other someone that I actually loved you like lovely
Let's turn against me
And we know he she does
I did it not you. Well, you can say whatever you want, Christine. Christine.
Can we play the rest of the clip? Do you see it?
Go for it. Yeah.
Tell me if I'm making fun of Christine at all or making fun of Chris.
I'll listen. I'll listen.
Just listen. Tell me if I'm making fun of Crystal or making fun of Christine.
Let's see. I want to hear from the chat.
Who are they making fool of themselves?
Crystal or Christine? And I was like, Christine, get on here. I want you to respond with...
I'm a neutral party here.
I know you're a neutral.
So the question is like...
The question is, if you're making fun of someone.
Christine or Crystal, okay?
You can just tell me.
Are we making fun of Christine or Crystal?
But she puts them in
We'll put them in these sex trafficking rings and we're in a friend probably fucking
And we're gonna get them all fucking caught real quick
Yeah, they're not trying to help people trying to get people
That's sick
Yeah, is that Joan River's talking?
Why do you think that she says that she's a part that she does sounds like Joan River
fucking listen
She says I'm listening that she is
What's it called, you know first aid what do you want?
To first aid and she also says that that she's
She's
First line security
Yeah, she said she's a security guard at the mall on the weekends, right?
No
No, she said that or is that what she told you?
She works with Alex at the mall
Well security
Maybe
But yeah, so she's she's falls into security so she can
Do other bad things with other parts of law. So yeah, she's fought
No, she's going to jail forever
I wouldn't really mind going to Jeff River, if it was me,
because I'd finally get like a city's five sex,
three showers, but, oh, but it's not a bad guy.
Yeah, but you're not a bad guy,
and you would like Excel because you're like a man,
but no, you're in.
I don't think I see it that I get in trouble though.
I think she's like, think it away with it.
I mean, you know those people that use the system,
you know, that say that they're doing,
companies and like
I follow you
And they say that they getting this people houses and they don't
and they got like they're giving the difference in so many money because
Yeah, you know, this is all fucking false and that fucking bitch is about to go down and she's about to have no job
Yeah, yeah, they're all doing bad, you know, it's it's about it's an all system. Oh
It's a bad system that's about to go down from Georgia to
There to Florida
What are they gonna do?
Well, they're about to get him to go to prison. So the floor Florida
Well, I don't know how that works
Who's gonna go first Epstein or
Christine
100%
We got to discuss every time we're talking about Christine and no
Well, because she did bad stuff online, and it's caught up to her.
But I imagine Christine doing anything bad online, where she was on a boat trip.
Well, because you can't pay people, you can't pay people to abuse you, people.
It's against the law.
Yeah, that's a long this is consensual right unless I say I want yeah, so and when it's on video and it's yeah
It's against a lot when it's been by five people
Yeah, and on different networks, we are not even the same fucking people so who is so who has a video of pristine like
It doesn't because we're not all the same
Well, we couldn't out because it's it's her work. It's what she did
It's out of her it's out of her her her own
Device Christina. I really hope that out of her own device. You know what you mean device, you know
When people do bad things under their own device
Yes
So you hacked Christine. Well, that's a little too
I would never know if she fucking hacked tried to do bad things to me
Christine I need you years ago years ago. I got this years ago. He doesn't even know I got all her shit years ago
How many years I told you this I told you this I tried to tell you this
This is why I did not want the fucking
Fagotry I said when when I said there's a thing with
Bag of tree, bag of tree.
Yeah, it's a tree stuff.
The tree of gods.
You don't even know what I know.
It's like a soul tree.
It's a tree.
It's like a god?
It's like a cabala now. It's a cabala.
Well, no, they have like...
You keep barking up that tree.
You know, they're friends with people
that aren't friends with us.
And you know...
Who are the terminals?
Yeah.
You do.
Thank you.
Mark us.
Let's watch the track.
Ladies and gentlemen, Limbiski and Snoop Dogg.
Freak baby, freak freak baby.
Red light, green light.
Are you ready to roll?
Tell me when you're ready to go.
Tell me when you're ready to roll.
Red light, green light.
Red light, green light, red light, green light
You ready to go?
Tell me when you're ready to go
I got the keys, baby
Put your mind at ease, baby
Go player, laying the cheese, baby
I know you're biting, biting my steez, baby
But I came, came to please, baby
Don't wait, wait, lay the grease, baby
Don't flake, flake, shake the knees, baby
Your fellas mad at me, baby
Oh well
enemies baby who's dragging they ragging on me baby who's dragging on me baby
he's my friend he's my friend i'm about to go to at least i'm chatterbait with that guy
actually we're gonna suck each other's dick
did you hear chris k is gonna once to come over and masturbate with me
well just be uh so i don't i don't like that
Well, I would say don't do that because he used one of the ones that was
What's the burning it's a gang that had like a lot of money to Murray?
Okay, let's not
Yeah, he came over there night and he's like hey like money talks he's like how does everyone want to see second
I do a chatter but then he said he says a lot of things and he acts a lot weird
Yeah
She's got like way more, I can tell she's very, I was told that he might just try to beat me up, but then I watched the video.
Mom, I'll be very aware, do be very aware.
So there was a time I did drugs on the stream, I did some ketamine.
Huh?
Or I took a line of ketamine, and then like I was talking to Kristen Marie.
Yeah, just looking at her face. I was like, oh my god, you have so much I could just seal like I think she just got like fresh
Fucking fillers or some shit
Well, I don't I mean I just don't know like
But I didn't mean to hurt anybody's feelings or anything okay guys what I do on this show is like
It's like what a with Chris K. It's like
Let people talk and then
Don't reveal themselves. I don't have to do much
Chris K. Like he'll like tell you that he's like he can play guitar, but he can't play like this
He's like a pretender like he's a delusional pretender dude like
It's terrible. I know a lot of these people are tenders like yeah
Well, it's like they found they found likes people that are like
go along with their fucking make-believe bullshit.
Have you heard of Cassandra?
No.
Mommy Cass?
I don't know about my Cass, but she's actually...
No, I'm talking about the IP2 chick.
I was in the Pappas. Oh.
Oh, yeah, her too, the handsomest thing.
Sondra was, she was like this princess and like all the little fellas in love with her.
And like, she like, I think I actually promised him a kiss, but then she didn't kiss him.
And so he spit in her mouth.
She was a psychic or she was a prophet or whatever, but the curse was that he spit in
her mouth that whatever she said would not be believed, even though it would be the truth.
I think Apollo spit in my mouth because
I'm talking the truth. I don't believe me. I can't believe I talk bullshit. Everyone believes them
What's the deal? I don't need to deal
You have no means to me tonight. Can't believe how mean she was. You're just mean
It's too big for me.
It's too big.
It's called Sweet Something.
Since I was in T.E.M.L.A.
I've found two thousand four-year-games
such a mistake.
Oh, Christine was me.
Christine was me.
Christine.
Oh, Christine.
How about this one, Mr. Request?
Play this song.
Play it, play it.
Camera, put it in the sky.
Maybe she doesn't have something here on midnight.
She doesn't have.
You
It's really big as we're going to be able to feel it.
Oh.
Why? Because I'm a Capricorn. I'm a Capricorn sun and rising.
I heard you just fine, because I'm taking off, I'm feeling a few hurts, I'm feeling like I'm going to show it to everybody.
Have a nice night guys.
Have a nice night.
Have a nice night, guys.
You're smooth, mystical
Yo, welcome to the Madness Buckele Insight